Ghost!
Stop running around!
I'm the female ghost here for your life.
I'm the male ghost here.
Boring.
I know what you're looking for.
Come with me, everyone.
Don't wander off again next time.
You hear me?
Give me a hand! Give me a hand!
Don't pull!
Easy, easy.
Easy now. Watch the steps.
Take it easy.
The steps! The steps!
My leg! My leg!
Slow down.
Why are you such a pain?
My leg!
Smells so good.
Is someone cooking?
Who'd be cooking in a place like this?
Wait.
Let's go.
Easy, easy, easy, easy.
Holy crap.
Young Master, what's going on here?
No way.
Why is there a banquet in this secret chamber?
Are these people all...
Miss.
What's wrong with you?
It's the Wan family's Yin-Yang Eyes.
Then she must be Wan Chun'er.
If the original Qi Family's Book of Talismans is truly hidden here,
then I've finally gathered the Talisman, Curse, Seal, and Eye.
Want to know?
See for yourself.
Food!
Go, go, go.
Don't move.
What?
Stop eating!
My tears haven't worn off, have they?
They haven't.
I can still see.
What are they doing?
A Feng Shui Killing Formation!
They're trying to...
...open the coffin to break the formation!
Chun'er!
Get ready!
Ghosts occupy the center, suppressing heaven and earth.
Open the coffin to dispel the evil!
Open the coffin!
Cousin Ling Yu.
What are you looking for?
Is this it?
What exactly do you want?
I'm here to marry you, of course.
Have you forgotten how you seduced me?
Stop playing dumb.
Qi Tiankun, you good-for-nothing!
A toad wanting to eat swan meat!
This good-for-nothing...
...is about to eat swan meat.
Take her away!
Qi Tiankun!
Li Xiao.
They hit you.
They beat you up, didn't they?
Does it hurt?
It hurts.
Jiushuang.
The Qi and Sheng families joined forces.
I didn't want them to hurt you too.
So I just took a few flesh wounds.
It's nothing serious.
What are you doing?
Miss Mei.
Our Qi family head invites you to the wedding.
Come at me instead!
Who the hell do you think you are?
Let go of me!
Jiushuang!
Let her go!
I said, let her go!
Jiushuang!
Help me up.
The original Qi Family's Book of Talismans.
Tianyou, look.
So the Wan family knew all along.
The Qi family wouldn't just hand over the original.
And specifically sent you to get it.
Young Master, how did you know it's a Yin-Yang Feng Shui formation?
Rats.
You didn't notice when we were outside, did you?
This place is a mine.
The so-called Feng Shui Killing Formation
is actually just the timing and terrain.
The magnetic field here is abnormal,
and the constant leak of Corpse Miasma
combine to mess with people's minds,
causing hallucinations.
The so-called "eye" in Yin-Yang Talismans
is actually just a medical prescription.
Taking it over a long period of time
will keep your mind clear
and unaffected by external factors.
However,
it requires someone with a special bloodline and physique
for it to be effective.
Ordinary people would lose their minds.
Are you the only one in the Wan family with Yin-Yang Eyes?
Everyone, be careful.
Watch your step.
Someone's coming.
Follow me.
Cousin Ling Yu,
how do you like this spot I chose for our wedding?
Isn't it quite original?
What is this place?
This was originally the Qi family's territory.
If my father hadn't been killed,
I wouldn't have risked coming here.
You guys, go clean up the secret room.
After we get married,
I'll take the Qi Family's Book of Talismans from the coffin.
Once we leave this place,
I'll be the head of both the Qi and Sheng families.
Young Master.
Qi Tiankun is such a psycho.
He's getting married in here?
I'm gonna kill him.
Don't move.
You can barely walk. Who are you gonna kill?
Keep it down.
Mr. Li, everything will be ready soon.
We've only been in here a short while,
and so much has happened outside.
Yeah.
Ling Yu must have been forced.
Where is the girl?
I'll go check.
Mr. Li.
I also locked Miss Mei in the right side chamber.
She'll witness the wedding shortly.
Well done.
Only if she sees it with her own eyes,
will the Mei family believe
that you control both the Qi and Sheng families.
Don't worry, Mr. Li.
Once the wedding is complete,
I'll immediately hand you the Qi Family's Book of Talismans.
This guy wanted to marry into our Wan family before.
Later, my brother kicked him out.
Now he's off hooking up with Mei Jiushuang from the Mei family.
He's trying to play all four families.
This secret room in the Qi family's back mountain sure is lively.
All four major families, Wan, Mei, Qi, and Sheng, are here.
Along with Young Marshal Li.
Let's go.
Let's go find Mei Jiushuang.
Sister Mei!
Chun'er.
Zhang Tianyou.
Sister Mei.
I have something to tell you.
Go ahead.
Li Xiao has been lying to you all along.
Why are you here too?
Special Corpse Miasma is starting to gather here again.
Miss Mei.
Just wait and enjoy the show.
Ground rat.
Move.
Cousin.
Qi Tiankun said you were dead.
Have my father's remains been taken care of?
On my wedding day,
I must bow to my Parents.
They've already been placed in the side chamber.
The secret room is almost ready too.
Master.
Should I prepare a bridal chamber for you as well?
You want me to consummate the marriage with the bride here?
Forgive me.
But it does sound quite thrilling.
It's a good idea.
Hurry up and go.
Right away!
I'll get it done immediately.